https://www.araize.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Araize Privacy Policy
Araize.com (this “Site”) is operated by Araize, Inc. (“Araize,” “we,” “us,” or “our”). This Internet Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) describes generally how Araize collects, uses, and transfers the personal information we collect through this Site. Because privacy laws vary from state to state within the United States and from country to country around the world, this Policy may be supplemented or amended by state or country-specific disclosures (“Privacy Notice(s)”), which will be provided to you at the time and on the page where you provide the personal information to which they apply. As used in this Policy and any Privacy Notice, the term “personal information” means information that identifies you personally, alone or in combination with other information available to us.
Your Consent
By using this Site, you are consenting to the collection, use, and transfer of your personal information as described in this Policy (and any Privacy Notices that apply to you). If you do not consent to the collection, use and transfer of your personal information as described in this Policy (and any Privacy Notices that apply to you), you may not use this Site.
This Privacy Policy May Change
Araize reserves the right to update or modify this Policy and any Privacy Notice, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of the Policy or Privacy Notice on this Site. If we modify this Policy or any Privacy Notice, the modifications will only apply to the personal information we collect after we have posted the revised Policy or Privacy Notice on this Site. For your convenience, when we modify this Policy we will post a notice informing users of the change for thirty (30) days on the home page of this Site.
Why We Collect Personal Information
Why do we collect your personal information? Because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services with a focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.
Your Choices
We respect your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use, and transfer your personal information. This Policy describes some of your choices. In most cases, we will ask you to indicate your choices at the time and on the page where you provide your personal information.
What Information Is Collected on this Site and How Is It Used?
When you access and use this Site, there are three ways we may collect information about you:
1. Information You Knowingly and Voluntarily Provide
Araize collects the information you knowingly and voluntarily provide when you use an Araize Internet Site, for example, the information you provide when you order an Araize product or service, download software, register for a course, subscribe to one of our free online newsletters, participate in one of our surveys, or when you ask us a question or send us feedback. In many cases, this information will include your e-mail address and other personal information. Araize uses this information for the purposes for which you provide it, for example, to confirm and fulfill your orders. If we are permitted to do so under applicable law, we may also use the information we collect through this Site for various other business purposes such as customer service, fraud prevention, market research, improving our products and services, and to contact you and your company with information and offers we believe may be of interest to you. In addition, we may remove all the personally identifiable information and use the rest for historical, statistical or scientific purposes.
Email Addresses
Araize collects e-mail address information from you when enter your e-mail address on this Site to order an Araize product or service, register for a course, subscribe to one of our free online newsletters, or participate in one of our surveys. Araize collects e-mail address information from you so that we may confirm and/or deliver your purchase; communicate with you regarding your order or registration; and alert you to other Araize programs, products, and services that may be of interest to you. Often times, our “topical” programs are only advertised through e-mail. You may “opt out” of receiving these e-mail notices at any time. To opt out of receiving email notices from us, please send an e-mail to unsubscribe@Araize.com. Please provide your name and email address so that we can identify your email address in our database and record your request.
2. Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser
As is true of most Web sites, Araize gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information typically includes the IP address of your Internet service provider, the name of your operating system (such as Windows® or Macintosh®); and the name and version of your browser (such as Internet Explorer®, Chrome®, Safari® or Firefox®). The information we receive depends on the settings on your web browser. Please check your browser if you want to learn what information your browser sends or how to change your settings. This type of information does not identify you personally. Unless you access this Site through an email we have sent you or have created a “user identity” by logging on during one of your visits, this information will not be linked to information that identifies you personally. We use this information to create statistics that help us improve our sites and make them more compatible with the technology used by our Internet visitors.
3. Information Collected By Placing a “Cookie” On Your Computer
Araize may obtain information about you by installing a “tag” on your computer’s hard drive. This tag is known as a “cookie.” Each time you visit this Site, our server will recognize the cookie. By assigning your computer a unique identifier, we are able to create a database of your previous choices and preferences and in situations where these choices or preferences need to be collected again, they can be provided by us automatically, saving you time and effort. For example, after you make your first purchase, if you decide to make another purchase, your shipping address will have been retained and will only need to be confirmed. We also use cookies to collect information about the ways visitors use our sites – which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page. We analyze this information (known as “clickstream data”) in statistical form to better understand our visitors’ interests and needs, to gather demographic information about our visitors and our user base as a whole, to identify trends, to administer this Site, and to improve the content and functionality of this Site. Most cookies do not expire when you close your browser; they stay on your computer until you delete them. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies, or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. Although you are not required to accept cookies when you visit this Site, you may be unable to use all of the functionality of the site if your browser rejects our cookies.
Sharing and Transferring Personal Information
Araize may share your personal information with other Araize business units. When we do so, these other Araize business units will use your information in the same manner we do. For example, if they are permitted to do so under applicable law, they may use the information we collected through this Site for market research, to improve their products and services, and to contact you and your company with information and offers they believe may be of interest to you. In addition, they may remove all the personally identifiable information and use the rest for historical, statistical or scientific purposes.
Araize may also share your personal information with companies we hire to perform support services for us, such as web hosting or credit card processing. These third parties are required by contract to use the personal information we share with them only to perform services on our behalf and to treat your personal information as strictly confidential. To learn which third-party service providers we use, please contact us at webmaster@Araize.com.
In certain, limited circumstances we may share or transfer personal information to unrelated third parties. For example, we may provide personal information to a third party (i) at your request; (ii) to comply with a legal requirement or court order; (iii) to investigate a possible crime, such as identity theft; or (iv) in connection with the sale, purchase, merger, reorganization, liquidation or dissolution of Araize or another Araize business unit. If such an event occurs, we will take appropriate steps to protect your personal information.
While it is in our possession, your personal information will generally be stored in Araize databases or databases maintained by our service providers. Most, if not all, of these databases will stored on servers and storage devices located in the United States. United States data protection laws may not provide as much protection as the data protection laws in force in your country. If you are located in a country outside the United States, by using this Site you consent to the transfer of your personal information to the United States.
Security of Personal Information
Although we maintain reasonable safeguards to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure, misuse or alteration, we cannot guarantee the security of systems that are connected to the Internet nor can we guarantee the security of information transmitted over the Internet.
Links to Third Party Internet Sites
This Site may contain links to other Web sites operated by Araize, or by one of our affiliates. It may also contain links to third-party Web sites that neither Araize, nor Araize’s affiliates control. This Policy applies only to personal information collected through this Site and does not apply to personal information collected on any other Web site operated by Araize, nor by Araize’s affiliates, nor to personal information collected on third-party Web sites. If you access other Web sites through a link on this Site, please take a few minutes to review the terms of use and privacy statement posted on each Web site you visit.
Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Araize aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.
If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us at sales@araize.com.
In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:
You have the right to update or to delete the information we have on you. . If you would like to make these changes, please contact us.
The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Araize relied on your consent to process your personal information.
Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.
You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).
Access to Personal Information
If you would like to review, correct and update the personal information you have provided to us through this Site, please contact us by email, postal mail or telephone at:
Araize
WEBMASTER
27 Kingswood Lane
Chapel Hill, NC 27517
webmaster@araize.com
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to comply with your request.
Retention of Personal Information
Araize retains the personal information collected on this Site as long as necessary to provide the services, products and information you request or as permitted by applicable law.
Governing Law
Araize is a United States corporation. The servers that support this Site are located in the United States of America. This Agreement shall be governed under the laws of the State of North Carolina, United States of America without regard to its conflicts of law provisions.
Questions about this Policy or our Data Practices
If you have questions or concerns about this Policy or any Privacy Notice, please contact us by email or postal mail at:
Get Started with FastFund Today!
